superstarmagazine.com 2013-06-05

# Privacy Policy | Superstar Magazine

**1\. General**

This policy covers all sites produced by Superstar London Limited (“Superstar London Limited”). Superstar London Limited is committed to safeguarding your privacy online. The purpose of this privacy policy is to inform you what personal information Superstar London Limited collects and the purposes for which it uses this information. This policy may change from time to time so please check back here periodically. In reviewing this privacy policy, please read our Website terms and conditions. If you wish to contact Superstar London Limited concerning any matter relating to your personal information then please also contact info@superstarlondon.co.uk.

You acknowledge that Superstar London Limited is exempt from data protection registration on the basis that all personal data collected is for the purpose of supporting its primary business activities such as advertising, marketing and public relations.

**2\. Disclosures**

Superstar London Limited may disclose your information, under strict terms of confidentiality and restriction of use, to partners of Superstar London Limited who supply services on behalf of Superstar London Limited and who need to process personal data in the provision of such services. When you use “Superstar London Limited Websites” you are consenting to the disclosure of your personal information to Superstar London Limited’s partners. Superstar London Limited will not disclose any of your personal information to any other third parties without your express consent. However, under certain circumstances the force of law may require the provision of information to legal authorities. In order to maintain the integrity of its website and safeguard the interests of its subscribers Superstar London Limited will comply with any such legally binding request.

**3\. Information Collected**

Identifiable information – Your information is collected when you register or fill in a form on a Superstar London Limited website, or you send an email to Superstar London Limited. The information that is provided by you will only be used for the purpose for which it is provided, unless you are informed otherwise at the time of giving the information. You may inform Superstar London Limited at any time if you wish Superstar London Limited to cease using your personal information.

Non-identifiable information – Superstar London Limited will from time to time collect information from you that does not reveal your personal identity. Superstar London Limited uses this information for editorial purposes, and occasionally for other internal purposes. This information is only used in aggregate form and is not connected to any name, address or other personal identifying information.

**4\. Use of personal information**

Superstar London Limited processes personal information for the purpose of providing a personalised service, conducting market research surveys, running competitions and providing you with information about products and services on offer. Superstar London Limited may from time to time use your contact information to tell you about news or events provided by Superstar London Limited or one of its strategic partners. You may opt-out of receiving such mailings, either when you register with Superstar London Limited or at any time afterwards. Superstar London Limited may also contact you with important information about your registration details even if you have opted-out of receiving promotional emails.

**5\. Use of Cookies**

Cookies are small amounts of information that are sent to and are stored on your computer. They are used to identify you when you visit the site, and to make your use of the site more convenient for you. Cookies are used to remember usernames, passwords and preferences and to deliver a faster and more personalised service.

The Superstar London Limited site and service may contain advertisements created and provided by a third party. These advertisements may place Cookies on your computer that collect information about you and your use of the Internet. Superstar London Limited does not control the collection or use of your information by such advertisers and this privacy policy does not apply to such information.

If you do not wish to have Cookies placed on your computer you can disable Cookies on your Internet browser. Turning them off however will mean that you will not be able to enjoy the Superstar London Limited web sites to their fullest.

**6\. Links**

There are links on Superstar London Limited web sites to third party web sites which Superstar London Limited has no control over. Superstar London Limited accepts no responsibility or liability for any third party practices on third party websites. Superstar London Limited advises you to carefully read 3rd party privacy statements prior to the use of any third party website.

**7\. International Transfers**

Due to the international nature of the Internet, the collecting and processing of your personal information in accordance with Superstar London Limited’s privacy policy will often involve transferring the data between countries in which Superstar London Limited, other companies in the Superstar London Limited group of companies and strategic partners are located (if any).

Superstar London Limited shall take steps to ensure that any transfer of data to a country or territory outside the European Economic Area, whose laws provide for a different standard of protection for your personal data than that provided under English law, shall be made subject to contractual arrangements which will require that your data be processed to at least a standard compliant with the Data Protection Act 1998.

**8\. Security**

This Website has security measures in place to protect against loss, misuse and alteration of your personal information under Superstar London Limited’s control. However no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure and whilst Superstar London Limited strives to protect your personal information, Superstar London Limited cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us and you do so at your own risk. Once Superstar London Limited receives the transmission, Superstar London Limited makes best efforts to ensure the security on the system.

**9\. Contact Details**

Superstar London Limited

International House,

124 Cromwell Road,

Kensington,

London

SW7 4ET

**10\. Subject Access Request**

Individuals who wish to discover the information held about them by Superstar London Limited may apply for a subject access request. The data controller may apply a fee of up to £10 to release the information.

Applications must be made in writing describing the information requested, stating the name of the applicant and an address for correspondence.

You also acknowledge that Superstar London Limited is entitled to ask for proof of identity (e.g. driver’s licence or telephone bill) to ensure that information is released to the correct person and further details may be requested to assist Superstar London Limited in finding the information (e.g. date of correspondence etc).

**11\. Additional**

**CHILDREN AND PARENTS**

Superstar London Limited is not intended for use by children, especially those under age 12. No one under age 12 is allowed to provide any personal information or use our public discussion areas, forums and chats. Minors between the ages of 12 and 17 must get the permission of their parent(s) or legal guardian(s) before making purchases, including subscriptions, on this site.

If your children disclose information about themselves in our public discussion areas, they may get unsolicited messages from other parties. Accordingly, you should tell them not to do so.

If you’re worried about your children’s activities or their privacy on our site, we encourage you to e-mail our Privacy Policy Coordinator at info@superstarlondon.co.uk.

If you have other concerns or questions about any aspect of this policy, you may also e-mail our Privacy Policy Coordinator. We welcome your feedback. You can also send us regular mail at the following address:

Privacy Policy Coordinator

Superstar London Limited

International House,

124 Cromwell Road,

Kensington,

London

SW7 4ET

**COMPETITIONS**

· Entrants must be at least 18 years of age and proof of age will be required before the prize is dispatched.

· All qualifying entrants who answer the question correctly will be placed in a free prize draw.

· Winners will be notified within 28 days of the draw taking place.

· There is no cash alternative to the prize.

· This competition is run by Superstar London Limited, and is not connected with Vogue magazine.

· The competition is not open to anyone associated with Superstar London Limited or any associated companies.

· The judges’ decision is final and no correspondence will be entered into.

A list of winners’ names is available on written request from Superstar London Limited.

· No responsibility can be accepted for entries which are not properly received due to communications beyond our control.

· Open to UK and Eire residents only.
